retweet.com 2010-12-04

# Retweet.com | News for the People, by the People!

Privacy Policy

[Retweet.com](http://retweet.com/) recognizes that its visitors, users, and others known collectively or individually as "Members" who use www.retweet.com the "Website" value their privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services and Web pages offered by [retweet.com](http://retweet.com/), or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies and details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Website.

Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide on the Website remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the [retweet.com](http://retweet.com/) Terms of Use.

Please note that any comment or other content you post or send to the Website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. Your messages and other information you make available in public areas of the [retweet.com](http://retweet.com/) website will be seen by people and organizations not related to or controlled by [retweet.com](http://retweet.com/), and may be used by others to contact you.

[Retweet.com](http://retweet.com/) Privacy Policy applies only to Websites and services that are owned and operated by Burleigh Operations LTD. While other Websites may be displayed as links from within [retweet.com](http://retweet.com/), those sites are owned and operated by others, and they may have different privacy policies. When linking from [retweet.com](http://retweet.com/) to other websites, if you have privacy concerns, we urge you to review the privacy policies of those sites.

  1. Information Collection and Use General 

Retweet.com does not require that you register in order to view its Content and User comments. 

Retweet.com collects personal information when you visit the Website and any time you provide information to [retweet.com](http://retweet.com/) about yourself. [retweet.com](http://retweet.com/) may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

[retweet.com](http://retweet.com/) automatically receives and records other non-personally-identifying information "Non-Personal Information" on our server logs from your browser even if you do not register with Retweet.com, for example, your IP address, Retweet.com cookie information, and the pages you visit.

Retweet.com uses Non-Personal Information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for content and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

  2. Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Retweet.com does not rent, sell, or share Personal Information with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide content or services youve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We use both your Personal Information and certain Non-Personal Information to improve the quality and design of the Website and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.

We may share Personal Information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Retweet.com Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

We may transmit Personal Information if Retweet.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. Keep in mind that any personal information, or comments that you voluntarily disclose on the Website, for example on comment pages becomes publicly available. Your account name is displayed to other Users when you send and/or post messages through the Website.

  3. Cookies and Web Beacons 

Retweet.com may set and access [retweet.com](http://retweet.com/) cookies on your computer. You may disable these cookies within your browser, but some portions of the Website may not work properly.

  4. Confidentiality and Security 

Retweet.com uses commercially reasonable technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any Personal Information you transmit to Retweet.com and you do so at your own risk.

We limit access to Personal Information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with Personal Information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

  5. Your Ability to Edit Your Account Information 

You can edit your Retweet.com account information at any time by visiting your account profile page.

We reserve the right to use your Personal Information in order to send you certain communications relating to the Retweet.com service, such as service announcements, and administrative messages, that are considered part of your Retweet.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

  6. International Users 

If you are a User accessing the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy as incorporated in our Terms of Use, you will be transferring your Personal Information into the United States and you consent to that transfer.

  7. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy 

Retweet.com may update this policy at any time in its sole discretion and without prior notice. We will strive to notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Retweet.com account and or by placing a notice on the Website.

  8. Effective Date 

This Privacy Policy was last modified August 19th, 2009.

  9. Contact Information 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, Please contact: david@retweet.com
